<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Ski Pass Selector</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="help_menu">Help</string>
    <string name="reset_title">Reset?</string>
    <string name="reset_button">Reset</string>
    <string name="earlyPassFlagTitle">Early bird pass prices?</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Calendar</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Graph</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Results</string>
    <string name="legend">N = night, A = all day, 4 = 4 hr, 8 = 8hr </string>
	<string name="footer">"<i>Tap a day, then select a ticket type</i>"</string>
	<string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
	<string name="reset_message">This will clear all tickets!</string>
	
	<string name="Season_pass">Season Pass</string>
	<string name="Adv_card">Advantage Card</string>
	<string name="Night_card">Night Club Card</string>
	<string name="NCC_w_AC">NCC with AC</string>
	<string name="Window_rate">Window Rate</string>
	
	<string name="help_contents">"Planning on taking some snow days this year?  Can’t decide which option is the best bang for the buck? \n
This app uses the 2013/14 rates for Liberty Mountain, Whitetail Mountain, and Roundtop resorts.  Just pick which days you’re planning on skiing, choose a ticket type for each day, and the app will do the math for you.\n 
There’s a toggle in the menu to choose between “early-bird” and full-price options for Season Passes and Advantage Cards.    If you purchase either of these passes before Nov. 1st, you’ll get the best savings. \n
You can only select one ticket type for any given day. \n
If you’d like to start over, there’s a reset option in the menu. \n \n

Known Issues in Ver. 1.0: \n
* The ticket menu pops up when scrolling through the calendar.  <i>It can be dismissed with the back button, or any click outside of the menu.</i> \n \n
* Tapping on the currently highlighted day does not bring up the ticket menu.  <i>Select a different day, dismiss the ticket menu, and reselect the desired day.</i> \n \n
* There’s no indicator on the calendar for days that have had a ticket added.  This is a limitation of the Android CalendarView widget, with no simple workaround available. \n \n
* Discounts for 2-day consecutive passes are not included." \n \n

<i>Press the back button to exit Help</i>
	</string>
</resources>
